[Music]
[音乐]
this is nick with logosbynic.com and in
我是logosbynic.com的尼克
this tutorial i'll be demonstrating how
在本教程中，我将演示
you can use the trace
您可以使用跟踪
bitmap feature located in inkscape and
Inkscape中的位图功能和
what trace bitmap does is it allows you
跟踪位图的作用是它允许您
to create a vector tracing of a
创建向量跟踪
photograph
照相
using an automated algorithm instead of
使用自动算法而不是
having to trace it manually using the
必须手动使用
bezier pen and other tools
贝塞尔钢笔和其他工具
okay now the benefit of using trace
好的，现在使用跟踪的好处是
bitmap is that it saves you a lot of
位图是它为您节省了大量
time it creates a really
时间它创造了一个真正的
quick tracing of any photograph you have
快速追踪您所拥有的任何照片
the downside of using it though
不过，使用它的缺点是
is that it doesn't always work with
它并不总是适用于
every photo based on the composition of
每一张照片都是基于
your photo sometimes it produces some
你的照片有时会产生一些
sloppy results so
草率的结果如此
you're never going to get a 100 accurate
你永远得不到100分的精确度
tracing of your photograph
追踪你的照片
unless you trace it manually but the
除非您手动跟踪它，但
downside of tracing it manually is that
手动跟踪的缺点是
it takes a lot of time and a little bit
这需要很多时间和一点时间
of expertise as well
专业知识也很丰富
so the method you should use depends on
因此，您应该使用的方法取决于
the image you're working with and what
你正在处理的图像以及什么
it is you're trying to achieve
这是你想要实现的
if you're just trying to create a quick
如果您只是想创建一个快速的
sloppy
草率
automated vector tracing of your photo
自动向量追踪您的照片
trace bitmap is great for that so let me
轨迹位图很适合这一点，所以让我
show you how to go about doing that i
告诉你怎么去做，我
have these two example photos here
这里有这两张示例照片
i'm going to work with this one first
我要先做这件事
i'm going to come over here to where it
我要到这里来，在那里
says
说
path i'm going to click on trace bitmap
我要点击轨迹位图的路径
now if you notice up here we have three
如果你注意到了，我们这里有三个
different tabs
不同的选项卡
trace bitmap pixel art and help
描摹位图像素图片和帮助
for this tutorial i'm going to focus on
在本教程中，我将重点介绍
trace bitmap pixel art would be a
跟踪位图像素艺术将是一个
separate tutorial altogether so let's
完全分开的教程，所以让我们
focus on trace bitmap for now
目前重点关注跟踪位图
if you notice in here we have two
如果你注意到我们这里有两个
different options we have single scan
不同的选项，我们有单次扫描
and we have multiple scans
我们有多次扫描
and the difference between the two of
以及两者之间的区别
them basically is one is for black and
他们基本上是一个是黑人和
white
白色
one is for color so single scan would
一种是颜色，这样一次扫描就可以
create a
创建一个
single vector object it would trace a
它将跟踪一个向量对象
single vector object over your photo
照片上的单个矢量对象
in one single color so it would be good
只有一种颜色，所以它会很好
for creating things like silhouettes
创造出像剪影这样的东西
or maybe even creating vector textures
或者甚至可以创建矢量纹理
whereas multiple scans would be good for
而多次扫描将有利于
creating
创造
uh vector tracings of photos that have a
呃，照片的矢量跟踪具有
lot of color and you want to retain some
颜色很多，你想保留一些
of that color so let me demonstrate how
所以让我来演示一下
each works i'm going to choose single
每一件作品我都会选择单曲
scan for this image because this is a
扫描此图像，因为这是
black and white image
黑白图像
and i just want to create like a like a
我只想创造一个像这样的
silhouette sort of tracing this
剪影就像是在追踪这个
now if you look at this drop down over
现在，如果你看一下这个下拉列表
here we have a lot of different options
在这里我们有很多不同的选择
and these
还有这些
options all what these options do is
选项所有这些选项的作用是
they basically
他们基本上
trace your image using a different
使用不同的工具跟踪您的图像
sort of algorithm and the one that you
一种算法，你可以用它
should use depends on the composition of
是否应该使用取决于组成
the image you're working with because
您正在处理的图像是因为
every image is different
每个图像都是不同的
okay so when you're tracing a bitmap
好的，当你追踪一个位图时
you're going to want to cycle through
你会想要循环通过
these different options
这些不同的选项
and update the preview to see how it
并更新预览以查看它如何
looks to find out which one is best for
希望找出哪一种最适合
your photo
你的照片
so for this one i'm just going to leave
因此，对于这一次，我将离开
the cut the brightness cut off i'm going
切断了亮度切断了我要走了
to click update
要单击更新，请执行以下操作
and it shows you a preview here of the
它向您展示了这里的预览
vector tracing that's going to be made
即将进行的矢量追踪
from the image
从图像中
okay that looks pretty good i like how
好的，看起来很不错，我喜欢这样
that looks i'm going to click ok to
看起来我要点击OK来
create the tracing
创建跟踪
and if you notice it created a vector
如果你注意到它创建了一个矢量
tracing
跟踪
over the photo now this here is a true
在这张照片上，现在这是一个真实的
vector object you can change the color
向量对象您可以更改颜色
of that
其中之一
you can perform path operations on that
您可以对其执行路径操作
you can do everything that you would
你可以做任何你想做的事
normally do with the vector object
通常处理向量对象
with this right here let me turn off
就在这里，让我关掉它
snapping now let me get rid of that
现在抓拍，让我摆脱它
let me show you some of these other
让我给你展示一些其他的
options here just to show you what i
这里的选项只是为了向你展示我的
mean if you come down here to like
我是说，如果你来这里
something like edge detection and you
比如边缘检测和你
click update you'll notice
点击更新，您会注意到
it doesn't really trace anything in the
它并没有真正追踪到
image there's some speckles
想象有一些斑点
caught in the uh in the tracing there
被困在，呃，在追踪中
but it's not really what i'm going for
但这并不是我真正想要的
so for this sort of image
因此，对于这类图像
edge detection wouldn't be good but
边缘检测不是很好，但是
maybe for a different type of image
也许是为了不同类型的图像
edge detection would work perfectly so
边缘检测将完美地发挥作用
really like i said it depends on the
真的就像我说的，这取决于
image you're working with so whenever
您正在使用的图像，因此无论何时
you're trying to trace vectors
你在试图追踪病媒
using this tool make sure to cycle
使用此工具时，请确保骑自行车
through these and see which one gives
通过这些，看看哪一个给了
you the best result
你是最好的结果
okay see this right here as an example
好的，请看这里作为一个例子
if i click ok
如果我点击确定
we end up with a pretty sloppy tracing
我们最终得到了一个相当草率的跟踪
this tracing right here it's also got a
这条轨迹在这里也有一个
lot of nodes in it this is a really
里面有很多节点，这真的是一个
complicated tracing so
如此复杂的追踪
uh one thing i'd like to warn you about
呃，有一件事我想警告你
when using this tool is to be very
当使用此工具时，将非常
careful
小心
about making complicated tracings like
关于进行复杂的跟踪，比如
this now my computer was able to handle
现在我的计算机可以处理这个问题了
this because i have a pretty powerful
这是因为我有一个相当强大的
computer but if you're using like your
计算机，但如果您像您的计算机一样使用
your average
你的平均水平
consumer grade computer this would
消费级计算机这将是
probably lock up
可能是锁上了
inkscape and cause you to have to
Inkscape，并导致您不得不
restart the application so
重新启动应用程序，以便
always be careful when you're creating
当你在创作的时候一定要小心
traces that you're not creating
不是你在创造的痕迹
something too complicated
一些太复杂的事情
okay so let me show you now if you go to
好的，现在让我演示给你看，如果你要去
uh any of these options
呃，这些选项中的任何一个
here brightness cutoff you have some
在这里，亮度切断，你有一些
settings that you can tweak over here
您可以在此处调整的设置
the brightness threshold let me update
亮度阈值让我可以更新
this
这
right now by default it's at 0.450 if i
现在默认情况下是0.450，如果
change that to something like point
将其改为类似POINT的内容
eight and click update it you can see it
八，然后点击更新，你可以看到它
changes
变化
the tracing it changes the algorithm of
它的跟踪改变了
the tracing there there's more of the
那里的追踪器有更多的
shadows being caught up in the tracing
在追踪中捕捉到的阴影
there
那里
so this is just one of those things that
所以这只是其中一件事
gives you more granular control over
为您提供更精细的控制
your tracing
你的踪迹
so when you're tracing an image just
所以当你追踪一幅图像时
cycle through these different settings
循环浏览这些不同的设置
see which one works best and then you
看看哪一个效果最好，然后你
can alter these settings a little bit to
我可以稍微更改这些设置以
see
看见
to really fine-tune your tracing now
现在要真正微调您的跟踪
this looked a lot better before
以前看起来好多了
at 0.45 so i'm going to put that back to
在0.45，所以我要把它放回
what it was and click update
它是什么，然后单击更新
and then over here we have invert image
然后在这里我们有反转的图像
if you click on that and you click
如果你点击它，然后点击
update
更新
you can see it creates an inverted
你可以看到它创建了一个倒置的
tracing if i click ok to create that
如果我单击确定以创建它，则跟踪
tracing
跟踪
it pretty much creates a vector tracing
它很大程度上创建了一个矢量跟踪
of the negative space
关于负空间的
and the subject it creates a vector
它所创造的主题是一个载体
tracing of the negative space of the
的负空间的追迹
image
图像
and the subject becomes the negative
而主体变成了否定的
space of the tracing as you can see
如您所见的轨迹空间
there
那里
okay so that's another thing you might
好的，这是你可能会做的另一件事
want to pay attention to whenever you're
想要在任何时候关注你
tracing an image so let me undo that
追踪一幅图像，让我撤销它
let me show you now how to trace images
现在让我向您演示如何跟踪图像
with color if i select this image right
如果我选对了这张图片，用颜色
here
这里
i'm going to click on multiple scans now
我现在要点击多个扫描
because i'm working with color
因为我在用色彩工作
and again we have all of these different
再一次，我们有所有这些不同的
options we can cycle through i'm going
我们可以循环的选项我要走了
to choose colors for this one
为这一件选择颜色
i'm going to click update and it's
我要点击更新，它是
showing you how the vector tracing would
向您展示向量跟踪将如何
look in color i'm going to click ok to
看彩色的，我要点击确定
generate that
产生那个
and as you can see here let me zoom in
就像你在这里看到的，让我放大
on this if you zoom out it looks
在这个上面，如果你把它放大，它看起来
photorealistic but if you zoom in you
照片逼真，但如果你放大你
can see that this is indeed a vector
可以看出这确实是一个矢量
tracing
跟踪
and now the flaws in using auto tracing
现在，使用自动跟踪的缺陷
become a little more apparent because
变得更加明显，因为
you can see there's a lot of
你可以看到有很多
imperfections in here there's a lot of
这里有很多不完美的地方
speckling and
斑点和斑点
a lot of details that got included in
很多细节都包含在
there that probably shouldn't have been
这可能是不应该出现的
but like i said with an auto tracing you
但就像我说的自动跟踪你
can't expect it to be perfect it's never
不能指望它是完美的，它永远不会
going to be
将会是
exact okay so let me come back over here
好的，让我回到这里来
this image over here we have the number
这张图片，我们有数字
of scans
扫描的数量
scans pretty much represent the number
扫描很大程度上代表了
of colors
颜色的
in an image okay so with this tracing i
在图像中，好的，所以有了这个跟踪，我
created eight scans meaning it's gonna
创建了八次扫描意味着它将
use eight different colors
使用八种不同的颜色
okay now if i decrease that to like
好的，现在如果我把它减少到喜欢
maybe something like three
可能是三个左右吧。
and click update it's only going to use
然后点击更新，它只会用到
three colors
三种颜色
okay as you can see there and inversely
好的，正如你所看到的，反之亦然
if i increase it from eight to maybe
如果我把它从8个增加到也许
something like 16
大概16岁左右
it includes more of the colors and if
它包含了更多的颜色，如果
you click ok
您可以点击确定
you end up with a bigger tracing with a
您最终得到了一个更大的跟踪，
lot of different options but at the same
有很多不同的选择，但都是一样的
time
时间
it looks a little more photorealistic
它看起来更逼真一点
and just to show you that this is indeed
只是想让你们知道这确实是
a vector tracing i'm going to ungroup
我要解开的一个向量追踪
this i'm going to go to object
这是我要去反对的
ungroup and it's going to ungroup it
解组，它将解组它
into lots of different little parts here
分成许多不同的小部分
and you could zoom in
你可以放大
and you could take these parts and
你可以把这些部分
change them and do whatever you want
改变它们，做你想做的任何事情
with them
和他们在一起
okay then finally if you click on this
好的，那么最后如果你点击这个
image up here you'll notice there's a
在这里的图像上，您会注意到有一个
remove background setting
删除背景设置
now if you enable that it's going to
现在，如果您启用它，它将会
remove the white background
去掉白色背景
from this image here the problem with
从这张图看，问题是
using this though is it it only works on
不过，使用这个是不是只能在
images
图像
where the background is really defined
在那里真正定义了背景
this image is a great example because
这张图片是一个很好的例子，因为
the background is white so if
背景是白色的，所以如果
the software will have no problem
软件将不会有任何问题
determining where the background is
确定背景的位置
located
设于
on more complex images it's just going
在更复杂的图像上，它只是在
to exclude areas of the image
排除图像区域的步骤
that it thinks is the background even if
它认为这是背景，即使
it's not exactly accurate so let me just
这不是很准确，所以让我
show you how that looks i'm going to
让你看看那是什么样子我要
click
单击
update i'm just going to click ok
更新我只需点击确定
and it created a vector tracing minus
它创造了一个向量跟踪减号
the background i'm going to place it
背景我要把它放在
over this object here so you can see
在这个物体上，所以你可以看到
okay now you get an idea i've removed
好了，现在你有一个想法了，我把它去掉了
the background now some of it
背景现在有一些了
some of it got wrong like you see here
就像你在这里看到的那样，有些地方是错的
there's a little bit of negative space
有一点负面的空间
in there showing through the image
在那里通过图像显示
beneath it is showing through there so
它下面是通过那里显示的，所以
it removes some of that as well but
它也去掉了一些东西，但是
that's okay because that's easy to fill
这没什么，因为它很容易填满
in
在……里面
otherwise but that's how that part works
否则，但这就是那部分的工作方式
and then finally down here we have some
最后在这下面我们有一些
settings that you can play with if
您可以在以下情况下使用的设置
if you've cycled through these options
如果您已经浏览过这些选项
and you've played with these
而你玩过这些
adjustments and you still can't get it
调整了，但你还是不能得到它
quite right
非常正确
you can adjust these as well we down
你可以把这些也调下来。
here we have speckles
我们这里有斑点
this says ignore small spots in the in
这是说忽略内侧的小斑点
the bitmap
位图
the idea behind this is that it
这背后的想法是它
eliminates some of this
消除了一些这样的问题
fragmentation in here some of these
这里有一些支离破碎的东西
speckles but as you can see it's not
斑点，但如你所见，它不是
always perfect
永远完美
maybe if i were to increase this a
也许如果我把这个增加到
little bit maybe it would do a little
一点点，也许它会起一点作用
better job but i'm not going to play
更好的工作，但我不会去玩
with that for now
现在就是这样
over here smooth corners that's enabled
在这里，启用了平滑的角落
by default whenever you create a vector
默认情况下，无论何时创建向量
tracing at something usually
追踪通常发生的事情
you end up with sharp corners in your
你的身体最后会出现尖锐的拐角
image they end up smooth when you trace
想象一下，当你追踪时，它们最终会变得光滑
them
他们
okay so uh that's enabled by default and
好的，那么，呃，这是默认启用的，
then over here optimize try to optimize
然后在这里优化，试着优化
paths by joining a paste
通过连接粘贴创建的路径
adjacent bezier curve segments the idea
相邻的Bezier曲线分割想法
behind that is that whenever you create
这背后的原因是，每当你创建
a vector tracing of an image
图像的矢量跟踪
you're creating a really complex uh
你在创造一个非常复杂的呃
vector object with a lot of nodes in it
包含大量节点的矢量对象
let me show you as an example here i'm
让我给你展示一个例子，我在这里
going to trace this image i'm going to
我要追踪这张图片，我要
click on this
点击此处
as you can see my computer is struggling
如你所见，我的电脑很吃力
with this a little bit i'm going to
有了这一点，我将
click on update
点击更新
i'll click ok now i may regret trying
我会点击OK，现在我可能会后悔尝试
this but i'm going to give it a try
但我要试一试
anyway i'm going to select this vector
不管怎样，我要选择这个向量
object and i'm going to come over here
反对，我要到这里来
to the edit paths by nodes tool
转到按结点编辑路径工具
okay now if you notice this image i mean
好的，如果你注意到这张图片，我的意思是
this
这
this vector object is made up of
此向量对象由
hundreds maybe even thousands of little
成百上千甚至几千
nodes here
此处的节点
okay now when you create a vector object
好的，现在当您创建一个矢量对象时
with lots of nodes like that
有很多这样的节点
um sometimes it'll lock up your computer
嗯，有时候它会锁住你的电脑
the idea behind optimize is that if you
优化背后的想法是，如果您
increase this threshold it'll create
增加它将创建的这个阈值
less of those nodes
这些节点较少
okay so that's pretty useful in creating
好吧，这对于创建非常有用
a vector tracing that you can actually
一种你实际上可以的载体追踪
work with without a crash in your system
使用时不会出现系统崩溃
but the downside is with less nodes it
但缺点是节点较少
may not be as accurate as a tracing
可能没有追踪那么准确
so i think that should do it for this
所以我认为这应该就够了
tutorial that is how you can go about
教程，这是您可以如何进行
uh creating vector tracings of
呃，创建
photographs
照片
using inkscape if you have any questions
如果您有任何疑问，请使用inkscape
leave a comment below and as always
在下面一如既往地留下评论
thanks for watching
感谢收看
[Music]
[音乐]